After automatically adjusting the version, keep the top.
With the new improvements of the automatic top tool,
now the costume can keep the same top structure after automatically adjusting the size,
including the number of vertices and the order of vertices.
First, add a virtual model,
then add a costume,
and then add a virtual model.
In the environment menu, you can open the display statistics.
In the lower left corner of the screen, you can see the statistics.
Now all costumes have 3676 vertices.
Next, replace the virtual model with a child model.
You can open the display frame according to your needs.
This way, you can see more clearly how the costume keeps the original top structure after automatically adjusting the version.
Select the automatic adjustment version and click on Keep Top in the pop-up window.
When the costume is re-dressed on the new virtual model,
you can see that the number of grid lines of the costume has not changed.
This function can also be used for your virtual model.
As long as you have a virtual model,
your virtual model has applied the information of the costume.
In the virtual model editor,
please make sure that your virtual model already has the information of the costume.
Please make sure that the costume is simulated and recorded on the previous virtual model
and the information of the costume of the virtual model.
To avoid errors in the automatic adjustment version,
or the automatic adjustment version function,
we can quickly complete the costume sharing and fitting between different characters.
The order of grid vertices will also continue to be maintained in the automatic adjustment version.
For example,
export three customized costume files
using the automatic adjustment version tool on different virtual models.
In other software,
they can be deformed or mixed deformed.
There will be no errors.
That's all for this video.
See you in the next video.